[{"answer": " Then answer my questions.  Where were you planning to stay during the two weeks that you're here", "docId": "15-Minutes.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Yes, we're in that place now.  But where are you planning to stay in that place", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Isn't he a little moody", "docId": "15-Minutes.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "In love?  With who", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": " Look.  Times Square.  Just like in the movies", "docId": "15-Minutes.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": " Why?  Why do I always have to speak to you in Czech", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Why you chasin' me, man", "docId": "15-Minutes.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "It's not my house, man.  I don't live here", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Turn that off!  Get the bags", "docId": "15-Minutes.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "For five years I paid for your stupidness", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Your sister said she didn't know where you were so you shouldn't write to her with return address if you're hiding", "docId": "15-Minutes.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "You know me...I never hurt anybody. Where's the money", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Nah, I musta missed it", "docId": "15-Minutes.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Well, just so you know, I don't care about that stuff", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "What if the tip was broken off", "docId": "15-Minutes.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "I think we've already found it", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Of course", "docId": "15-Minutes.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I wanted to run up to a building on fire, kick in the door, rush into the smoke and save a kid", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Yeah.  Now's not a good time", "docId": "15-Minutes.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Alright", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Alright", "docId": "15-Minutes.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Alright", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Alright", "docId": "15-Minutes.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Alright", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Well, that's great", "docId": "15-Minutes.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "No.  Go ahead.  You're gonna be great", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Yeah.  I'll do that.  As long as you're not patronizing me", "docId": "15-Minutes.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "I love you", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Tonight", "docId": "15-Minutes.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Yeah.  I promise", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "I came here.  I had no money.  I knew no one.  I couldn't get a job because you have to have a green card to get work. They approached me", "docId": "15-Minutes.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "What are you asking me", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "The video of my friend and my friend", "docId": "15-Minutes.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "And the whore's murder?  You didn't erase that either, did you?  Don't lie, I won't be angry", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "What do you mean, 'cleaned up?", "docId": "15-Minutes.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "A shower!?  Did you take one, too", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Come to 45 Broadway.  Don't bring the Police.  Come alone or you'll be in my next film", "docId": "15-Minutes.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "No.  I'm the best that's ever threatened you", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Is he your boyfriend", "docId": "15-Minutes.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "If I was your boyfriend, I might be", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "A good Immigration lawyer could stall the process.  my friend recommended one", "docId": "15-Minutes.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "I'm glad I met you", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "Oh no!  No!  Shit", "docId": "15-Minutes.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "He has the camera!  He took the movie", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "Where are we going", "docId": "15-Minutes.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "Yes.  Yes, come with me", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "Tell me about yourself.  What you did as a young boy... what your parents were like", "docId": "15-Minutes.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "Your mother was blind", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "Your father put cigarettes out on you", "docId": "15-Minutes.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "Can I see your back", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "Oh, my friend", "docId": "15-Minutes.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "I don't think it's abuse, I think it's torture", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "Chief", "docId": "15-Minutes.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "End my career", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "Forget about me.  You have enough problems of your own", "docId": "15-Minutes.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "I don't want to drag you down with me", "qsentId": 56}]